Ayu Andini, S.KOM

Kp.Waluran RT.01 RW.04 087809502596 ayuan841@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/ayu -andini-159131255/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a fresh graduate who has accustomed to using various applications such as Microsoft Office, Figma, Canva and Visual Studio Code. Discipline and able to work well in a team. I have project experiences such as application development for my final project, make a website for exportir and some project UI design for mobile aplication.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

STTIKOM INSAN UNGGUL

Cilegon, Banten Informatics engineering 2022

SMAN 1 ANYAR

Anyer,Serang-Banten science 2015

PROFICIENCIES

- HTML
- CSS
- Ms.Office
- Figma
- Wordpress
- UI UX design
- Active listener
- Teamwork
- Discipline
- Time management
- Adaptable

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

PT.Permata Digital (Remote) UI UX Design

May 2023 - December 2023

- I worked on a client project in the form of creating a mobile application UI design for document creation services using the figma application.
- I worked on a client project in the form of creating a UI/UX website design and mobile application for Arroudloh Islamic Boarding School using the figma application.

Therapyst Amira Aesthetic Clinic

November 2015 - March 2023

- I did facials
- A doctor's assistant when the doctor was performing treatment and prepared the tools needed during the treatment.
- and promote available products and treatments

Store assistant Store Mojito's

April 2020-December 2022

- I am responsible for assembling and sorting goods in the store.
- Promote mojitos shops through social media in 2020-2022